Guide to the Records of the NYU TV and Media Services Video Recordings RG.38.16.1
New York University Archives
- Series I: Video Recordings, 1993-2005; 219087
  - NYU Portraits, 29 Sep 2008; cuid1577; 243451; 2 minidvs (Box 81)
  - 50th Anniversary of Brown vs. Board of Education lecture/panel, 17 May 2004; cuid1578; 219037; 3 videocassettes (Box 23, Reel Project 79)
    Barcode: 31142042272966
  - Stern Barcelona 2009: Global Alumni, 12 Jun 2009; cuid1579; 245088; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - SCPS: McGhee "Online Interviews", 21 Jan 2009; cuid1580; 245089; 7 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - Center for Ancient Studies (CAS): Writing, 24 Apr 2009; cuid1581; 245090; 13 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - Congressional Oversight Hearing, 28 May 2009; cuid1582; 245091; 3 dvd-r disks (Box 86)
  - Fales Food Series: "NY Farm Connections", 4 Apr 2009; cuid1583; 245092; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - Bankruptcy and the Financial Crisis, 30 Jun 2009; cuid1584; 245093; 6 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - Reading Recovery Program Graduation, 5 Jun 2009; cuid1585; 245094; 2 dvd-r disks (Box 86)
  - Reality Show, 26 Aug 2009; cuid1586; 245095; 5 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - NYU Portraits: Voices of a People, 26 Aug 2009; cuid1587; 245096; 5 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - College of Arts and Science Deans Lecture, 17 Sep 2009; cuid1588; 245097; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - President's Welcome and Reality Show, 31 Aug 2009; cuid1589; 245098; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - President's Welcome and Reality Show, 31 Aug 2009; cuid1590; 245099; 2 dvd-r disks (Box 86)
  - New York Metropolitan Transportation Council, 24 Sep 2009; cuid1591; 245100; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - Constitution Day, 14 Sep 2009; cuid1592; 245101; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - Center for Ancient Studies: Legitimating Violence Execution, Human Sacrifice, Assassination, 24 Sep 2009; cuid1593; 245102; 14 dvd-r disks (Box 86)
  - Center for Ancient Studies: Legitimating Violence Execution, Human Sacrifice, Assassination, 24 Sep 2009; cuid1594; 245103; 8 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - Development Research Institute (DRI): What Would the Poor Say? Debateds in Aid Evaluations, 6 Feb 2009; cuid1595; 245104; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - The Children of Buroughs: New York Archives, 8 Oct 2009; cuid1596; 245105; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - The Unbearables, 24 Sep 2009; cuid1597; 245106; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - Drug-Resistant TB and HIV/AIDS in Southern Africa: Human Rights, Evidence, and the Public Good, 8 Oct 2009; cuid1598; 245107; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - Churchill School Graduation, 29 Jun 2009; cuid1599; 245108; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - Churchill School Graduation, 29 Jun 2009; cuid1600; 245109; 1 dvd-r disks (Box 86)
  - Steinhardt TACD Workshop Marco Center, 29 Sep 2009; cuid1601; 245110; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - Steinhardt TACD Workshop Marco Center, 29 Sep 2009; cuid1602; 245111; 4 dvd-r disks (Box 86)
  - Music and Performing Arts Professions: Meeting on Disproportionality in Special Education, 9 Cct 2009; cuid1603; 245112; 5 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - Student Health Center: H1N1 Forum, 14 Oct 2009; cuid1604; 245113; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - Creative Writing Program: Dance Program, 14 Dec 2008; cuid1605; 245114; 3 dvd-r disks (Box 86)
  - Alumni Weekend: Happy Hour and Raffle, 3 Oct 2009; cuid1606; 245115; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - Billy Collins Reading, 1 Sep 2009; cuid1607; 245116; 2 dvd-r disks (Box 86)
  - CAS Freshman Convocation, 31 Aug 2009; cuid1608; 245117; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - CAS Parent's Day Video Overflow Simulcast, 17 Oct 2009; cuid1609; 245118; 2 dvd-r disks (Box 86)
  - CAS Parent's Day Video Overflow Simulcast, 17 Oct 2009; cuid1610; 245119; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - Nursing Workshop, 1 Sep 2009; cuid1611; 245120; 2 dvd-r disks (Box 86)
  - Reynolds Speaker Series: Seth Goldman President and TeaEO of Honest Tea, 19 Oct 2009; cuid1612; 245121; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - Remarque Lecture: Tony Judt, 19 Oct 2009; cuid1613; 245122; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - E.L. Doctorow Reader from "Homer and Langley", 22 Oct 2009; cuid1614; 245123; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - Everything You Wanted to Know (and Didn't) About Film Festivals, 3 Nov 2009; cuid1615; 245124; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 87)
  - Julie Shifman Presentationa at NYU, 9 Nov 2009; cuid1616; 245125; 1 dvd-r disks (Box 87)
  - Julie Shifman Presentationa at NYU, 9 Nov 2009; cuid1617; 245126; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 87)
  - Peter Orszag, 3 Nov 2009; cuid1618; 245127; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 87)
  - Annual Leon Levy Lecture, 5 Nov 2009; cuid1619; 245128; 2 minidvs (Box 87)
  - Medical Education Matters: A Theory Building Conference, 11 Nov 2009; cuid1620; 245129; 6 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 87)
  - Frumkes Lecture in Philosophy: Philip Kitcher, 16 Nov 2009; cuid1621; 245130; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 87)
  - Courant Institute Alumni Presentation, 13 Nov 2009; cuid1622; 245131; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 87)
  - MLK Keynote Event: Howard Zinn, 21 Jan 2010; cuid1623; 245132; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 87)
  - "You are Cordially Invited": the Art and Influence of Robert Blanchon, 2010 Jan 26; cuid1624; 245137; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 87)
  - Columbian Consulate Webcasts, 2010 Aug 8; cuid1625; 245138; 5 dvd-r disks (Box 87)
  - NYU Schack Institute of Real Estate Press, 2010 Jan 10; cuid1626; 245145; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 87)
  - National College Depression Partnership, 2000 Jan 15; cuid1627; 245146; 24 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 87)
  - 11th Annual Irving H. Jurow Lecture, 2010 Feb 2; cuid1628; 245147; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 87)
  - Fales Food Series: Italian Food in New York, 2010 Feb 3; cuid1629; 245351; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 87)
  - David Wonjnarowicz Photographer, 2010 Feb 4; cuid1630; 245352; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 87)
  - Humanities: Thinking Through Violence, 2010 Feb 9; cuid1631; 245353; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 88)
  - Reynolds Speaker Series: Karl Hoffman, 2010 Feb 16; cuid1632; 245354; 2 minidvs (Box 88)
  - Reynolds Speaker Series: Karl Hoffman, 2010 Feb 16; cuid1633; 245355; 1 dvd-r disks (Box 88)
  - Will Wright, 2010 Feb 17; cuid1634; 245356; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 88)
  - SCPS Schack Online Interviews, 2010 Jan 21; cuid1635; 245357; 6 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 88)
  - CGA Public Events Series, 2010 Feb 17; cuid1636; 245358; 1 minidvs (Box 88)
  - SCPS Podcast: Bjorn Hanson, 2010 Feb 22; cuid1637; 245359; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 88)
  - Schack Panel "Real Estate: A Local Business", 2010 Feb 23; cuid1638; 245360; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 88)
  - Reynolds Speaker Series: Chris Jordan, 2010 Feb 23; cuid1639; 245361; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 88)
  - Ultraviolet Live, 2010 Feb 25; cuid1640; 245362; 5 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 88)
  - Google versus Apple: Who Will Win?, 2010 Mar 2; cuid1641; 245363; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 88)
  - Mabou Mines Opening Night Reception, 2010 Mar 4; cuid1642; 245364; 2 dvd-r disks (Box 88)
  - Remappings: Asia/Pacific/America, 2010 Mar 5; cuid1643; 245365; 12 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 88)
  - Steinhardt Symphony Orchestra, 2010 Mar 8; cuid1644; 245366; 5 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 88)
  - Fales: Through Other Lenses, 2010 Mar 9; cuid1645; 245367; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 88)
  - Hartford Institute: voice over recording, 2010 Mar 8; cuid1646; 245368; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 88)
  - New York Metropolitan Transportation Council, 2010 Mar 18; cuid1647; 245369; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 88)
  - Annual Fales Lecture, 2010 Mar 11; cuid1648; 245370; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 88)
  - GME Program Director' Retreat Resident, 2010 Mar 22; cuid1649; 245371; 9 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 88)
  - Nursing Conference: Innovative Applications, 2010 Mar 19; cuid1650; 245372; 6 dvd-r disks (Box 88)
  - Fales Food Series: Food Media in New Media, 2010 Mar 25; cuid1651; 245373; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 88)
  - UN: Bill Clinton Speaks about Haiti, 2010 Mar 25; cuid1652; 245374; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 88)
  - Reynolds Social Entrpreneruship in the 21st Century, 2010 Apr 1; cuid1653; 245375; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 88)
  - Vitamin A Deficiencies and Global Public Health, 2010 Mar 30; cuid1654; 245376; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 88)
  - Stern School of Business, Social Impacting, 2010 Apr 5; cuid1655; 245377; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 88)
  - Ashok Sani Lecture: Mark K. Shriver, 2010 Apr 6; cuid1656; 245378; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 89)
  - Unigo.com Wall Street Journal Panel, 2010 Apr 6; cuid1657; 245379; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 89)
  - University Professorship Lecture, 2010 Apr 6; cuid1658; 245380; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 89)
  - Global Public Health: Mexico, 2010 Apr 9; cuid1659; 245381; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 89)
  - Teaching with Technology, 2010 Apr 16; cuid1660; 245382; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 89)
  - New York University's Frederic Ewen, cuid1661; 245383; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 89)
  - SCPS Schack Career Fair, 2010 Apr 20; cuid1662; 245384; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 89)
  - Courant Alumni Lecture, 2010 Apr 20; cuid1663; 245385; 1 minidvs (Box 89)
  - Reynolds Speaker Series: Anthony Romero, 2010 Apr 27; cuid1664; 245478; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 89)
  - Stern International Studies Program: ISP, 2010 Apr 30; cuid1665; 245479; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 89)
  - Africa House: The Rule of Law and Business in Africa, 2010 May 3; cuid1666; 245480; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 89)
  - Courant Lecture: Alfio Quarteroni, 2010 Apr 29; cuid1667; 245481; 1 minidvs (Box 89)
  - Fales Food Series: Me in a Book, 2010 Apr 29; cuid1668; 245482; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 89)
  - International Public Policy Forum, 2010 Apr 17; cuid1669; 245483; 6 dvd-r disks (Box 89)
  - Global Health Capstone Presentations, 2010 May 7; cuid1670; 245484; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 89)
  - Courant Institute of Mathmatical Science Lecture, 2010 May 8; cuid1671; 245485; 6 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 89)
  - The Mysteries and Marvels of Memory, 2010 Mar 27; cuid1672; 245486; 11 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 89)
  - SCPS Presentation: Naomi Zigler, 2010 Apr 14; cuid1673; 245487; 1 minidvs (Box 89)
  - Fales Food Series: Feed Your Pet Right, 2010 May 27; cuid1674; 245488; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 89)
  - CAS Stuyvesant Intel Presentations, 2010 May 27; cuid1675; 245489; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 89)
  - CAS Stuyvesant Intel Presentations, 2010 May 27; cuid1676; 245490; 3 minidvs (Box 89)
  - Secret Gardens: Powerful Plots in Surprising Places, 2010 Jun 17; cuid1677; 245491; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 89)
  - NYU Libraries All Staff Meeting, 2010 Jun 21; cuid1678; 245492; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 89)
  - Churchill School Graduation, 2010 Jun 25; cuid1679; 245493; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 89)
  - BARD High School Early College, 2010 Jun 24; cuid1680; 245494; 1 dvd-r disks (Box 89)
  - MetroCenter's 2010 Technical Assistance, 2010 Jul 9; cuid1681; 245495; 6 dvd-r disks (Box 89)
  - Institute of Art and Civic Dialogue: Anna Deavere Smith, 2010 Oct 16; cuid1682; 245498; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 90)
  - CAS Parent's Day Video Overflow, 2010 Oct 23; cuid1683; 245500; 2 dvd-r disks (Box 90)
  - Fales: Mary Ellen Solt Reading, 2010 Oct 27; cuid1684; 245501; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 90)
  - Interactive Arts Performance Series: Ear to the Earth, 2010 Oct 27; cuid1685; 245502; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 90)
  - Derek Jeter Podcast, 2010 Oct 28; cuid1686; 245503; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 90)
  - Frumkes Lecture in Philosophy: Amartya Sen, 2010 Nov 4; cuid1687; 245504; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 90)
  - Fales Food Series: Back into the Kitchen, 2010 Nov 4; cuid1688; 245505; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 90)
  - George Stoney Tribute, 2010 Nov 4; cuid1689; 245506; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 90)
  - Casa Italiano Anniversary, 2010 Nov 4; cuid1690; 245507; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 90)
  - Courant Alumni Lecture: Vladimir Vapnik, 2010 Nov 9; cuid1691; 245508; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 90)
  - Silver School of Social Work: 50th Anniversary, 2010 Nov 11; cuid1692; 245509; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 90)
  - Tamiment Library: Philip Agee, 2010 Nov 9; cuid1693; 245510; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 90)
  - Pedagogy and Theatre of the Oppressed, 2010 Nov 12; cuid1694; 245511; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 90)
  - Commonweal Magazine Conversations, 2010 Nov 12; cuid1695; 245512; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 90)
  - Tisch School of the Arts Parents Day Simulcast, 2010 Oct 23; cuid1696; 245513; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 90)
  - DNP Leadership Class Lecture, 2010 Nov 21; cuid1697; 245514; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 90)
  - Reynolds Speaker Series: Martin Fischer, 2010 Nov 29; cuid1698; 245515; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 90)
  - Jacob J. Javits Visiting Professorship, 2010 Dec 7; cuid1699; 245517; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 90)
  - The Women's Conference, 2010 Oct 26; cuid1700; 245519; 2 dvd-r disks (Box 90)
  - A Conversation with Gordon Brown, MP, 2010 Dec 14; cuid1701; 245520; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 90)
  - New Trustee Induction Ceremony, 2010 Dec 13; cuid1702; 246016; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 90)
  - The Future of Nursing with Kristie Gebbie, 2010 Dec 13; cuid1703; 246017; 1 minidvs (Box 90)
  - Courant: 75th Anniversary Holiday Lecture, 2010 Dec 16; cuid1704; 246018; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 90)
  - An Evening with Senators Tom Daschle and Trent Lott, 2011 Feb 2; cuid1705; 246019; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 90)
  - America at a Crossroads: The dayton Accords, 2011 Feb 9; cuid1706; 246020; 8 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 90)
  - Sheikh Mohamad bin Zayed Scholars Program, 2011 Feb 5; cuid1707; 246021; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 91)
  - A/P/A: Midnight on the Mavi Marmara, 2011 Feb 16; cuid1708; 246022; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 91)
  - Third Annual Global South Asia Conference, 2011 Feb 16; cuid1709; 246023; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 91)
  - Stern: Social Impacting Corporate Social, 2011 Mar 21; cuid1710; 246024; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 91)
  - SCPS: McGhee Egyptian Panel, 2011 Mar 22; cuid1711; 246025; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 91)
  - Reynold Speaker Series: Food Panel, 2011 Mar 23; cuid1712; 246026; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 91)
  - PLACEMARKER BOX 92, cuid1713; 246032 (Box 92)
  - Starworks Foundation Showcase with Jonathan Safran Foer and Matthea Harvey, 2011 Apr 8; cuid1714; 246090; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - Fales: What's the Matter With Mass Produced?, 2011 Apr 14; cuid1715; 246127; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - Fales: Visual Aids, What Comes Next?, 2011 Apr 20; cuid1716; 246128; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - NYU's Inaugural Distinguished Global leader Residence, 2011 Apr 4; cuid1717; 246097; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - Courant Lecture: The Search for Randomness, 2011 Apr 7; cuid1718; 246098; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - Presidents Service Awards, 2011 Apr 27; cuid1719; 246099; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - Wagner: Gordon Brown at Stern, 2011 Apr 8; cuid1720; 246100; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - Stern: Entrepreneur Competition Awards Final Pitch and Ceremony, 2011 Apr 29; cuid1721; 246101; 6 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - UDAR: Alumni Luncehon University Development and Alumni Relations, 2011 Apr 6; cuid1722; 246102; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - Courant 75th Anniversary Celebration, 2011 May 6; cuid1723; 246104; 9 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - Business and White Collar Crime, 2011 Apr 25; cuid1724; 246106; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - Institute of Public Knowledge Conference: Designing Mobility for Democracy: The Role of Cities, 2011 Apr 14; cuid1725; 246108; 6 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - NYU Trustee's Pre Commencement Dinner, 2011 May 17; cuid1726; 246109; 6 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - Courant Summer Conference "Games for Change", 2011 Jun 20; cuid1727; 246110; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - Churchill School Graduation, 2011 Jun 24; cuid1728; 246111; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - Stern Lunchtime Leadership Speaker Series, 2011 May 26; cuid1729; 246112; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - Stern ISP: Final Presentation Competition, 2011 May 6; cuid1730; 246113; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - Speakers on the Square: Mossette Broderick American Guilded Age, 2011 Jun 13; cuid1731; 246114; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - Metro Centeres Technical Assistance Center of Disproportionality, 2011 Jul 6; cuid1732; 246115; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - SCPS Media Talk Magazines:The New Conversations, 2011 Jun 14; cuid1733; 246117; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - Learning Leaders: Real Superheroes of NYC Public Schools, 2011 May 11; cuid1734; 246118; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - Trends in Literary Translation, 2011 Apr 16; cuid1735; 246123; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - Stern Entreprenuer Competition Awards, 2011 Apr 29; cuid1736; 246124; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - Fales: From Here to Harvesting, 2011 Jun 9; cuid1737; 246126; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - Welcome Week Class of 2021 Recording, Including Address by Former Dean of Admissions Shawn Abbott, 2017; cuid1738 (Box Electronic Records, E-records UA_RG_38-16-1-1_ER_1)
- Series II: Commencement and Founder's Day, 1995-2009; 219016
  - 163rd NYU Commencement, 1995; 219086; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 16, Reel Project 74)
    Barcode: 31142042272891
  - Commencement & Founder's Day Videotapes 1995, 219085; 33 videocassettes (Box 27)
  - Commencement & Founder's Day, 1996; 219084; 20 videocassettes (Box 28)
  - Founder's Day, 1997; 219083; 1 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 13, Reel Project 63)
    Barcode: 31142042272867
  - Gallatin Commencement, 1997; 219164; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 5, Reel Project 19)
  - Gallatin Commencement, 1997; 243455; 1 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 5/Reel Project 19)
  - Gallatin Commencement, 1997; 243456; 1 videocassettes (Box 5/ Project Reel 18)
  - Gallatin Commencement, 1997; 219082; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 16, Reel Project 72)
  - 165th NYU Commencement, 1997; 219081; 2 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 16, Reel Project 73)
    Access copy
    Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 12:20
  - Bagpipes for Commencement, 1997; 219080; 1 sound cassettes (Box 21 / Reel Project 77)
    Barcode: 31142042272941
  - Commencement & Founder's Day, 1997; 219079; 14 videocassettes (Box 29)
  - Commencement & Founder's Day Videotapes, 1997; 219078; 9 videocassettes (Box 30)
  - Grad Alley, 1998; 219077; 3 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 13, Reel Project 65)
  - 166th NYU Commencement: JumboTron, 1998; 219076; 1 videocassettes (Box 13, Reel Project 66)
  - Founder's Day, 1998; 219075; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 14, Reel Project 63)
    Barcode: 31142042272875
  - 166th NYU Commencement, 1998; 219074; 4 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 16, Reel Project 66)
  - Stern Undergraduate Pre-commencement Footage, 1998; 219073; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 21, Reel Project 64)
  - NYU Grad Alley, 1998; 219072; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 19, Reel Project 65)
    Barcode: 31142042272925
  - Commencement & Founder's Day Videotapes, 1998; 219071; 23 videocassettes (Box 31)
  - Commencement & Founder's Day Videotapes, 1998; 219070; 13 videocassettes (Box 32)
  - Commencement & Founder's Day Videotapes, 1998; 219069; 9 videocassettes (Box 33)
  - Commencement & Founder's Day Videotapes, 1998; 219068; 8 videocassettes (Box 34)
  - Founder's Day, 1999; 219067; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 13, Reel Project 63)
  - Founder's Day Master, 1999; 219066; 2 videocassettes (Box 15, Reel Project 63)
    Barcode: 31142042272883
  - 167th NYU Commencement Master, 1999; 219065; 1 videocassettes (Box 16, Reel Project 71)
  - 167th NYU Commencement, 1999; 243452; 2 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 16, Reel Project 71)
  - Commencement & Founder's Day, 1999; 219064; 11 sound discs (minidisc) (Box 35)
  - Commencement & Founder's Day Videotapes, 1999; 219063; 9 videocassettes (Box 36)
  - Commencement & Founder's Day Videotapes, 1999; 219062; 11 videocassettes (Box 37)
  - Stern Undergraduate Precommencement, 2000; 219061; 1 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 13, Reel Project 64)
  - 168th NYU Commencement, 2000; 219060; 10 videocassettes (Box 13, Reel Project 67)
  - 168th NYU Commencement, 2000; 219059; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 14, Reel Project 67)
  - 168th NYU Commencement, 2000; 243453; 2 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 14, Reel Project 67)
  - Stern Graduation, 2000; 219058; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 14, Reel Project 64)
  - Founders Day, 2000; 219057; 2 videocassettes (Box 15, Reel Project 63)
  - Gallatin Commencement Master, 2000; 219056; 2 videocassettes (Box 16, Reel Project 72)
  - School of Continuing & Professional Studies Commencement, 2000; 219055; 2 videocassettes (Box 16, Reel Project 75)
  - 169th NYU Commencement, 2001; 219054; 3 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 14, Reel Project 70)
  - Founder's Day, 2001; 219053; 3 videocassettes (Box 15, Reel Project 63)
  - 169th Commencement Exercises NYU 2001, 10 May 2001; 231833; 2 videocassettes (Box 68)
  - 169th NYU Commencement Master, 2001; 219052; 4 videocassettes (Box 16, Reel Project 70)
  - 169th NYU Commencement Master, 2001; 219051; 11 videocassettes (Box 17, Reel Project 70)
    Barcode: 31142042272909
  - 169th NYU Commencement, 2001; 219050; 10 videocassettes (Box 18, Reel Project 70)
    Barcode: 31142042272917
  - Gallatin Commencement Master, 2001; 219049; 2 videocassettes (Box 19, Reel Project 72)
  - "School of Continuing & Professional Studies Class Day Exercises Master, 2001; 219048; 1 videocassettes (Box 19, Reel Project 69)
  - Founder's Day, 2002; 219047; 3 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 13, Reel Project 63)
  - 170th NYU Commencement, 2002; 219046; 2 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 13, Reel Project 68)
  - Founder's Day, 2002; 219045; 4 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 14, Reel Project 63)
  - Founder's Day Master, 2002; 219044; 3 videocassettes (Box 15, Reel Project 63)
  - School of Continuing & Professional Studies Commencement Master, 2002; 219043; 4 videocassettes (Box 19, Reel Project 69)
  - 170th NYU Commencement, 2002; 219042; 8 videocassettes (Box 19, Reel Project 68)
  - 170th NYU Commencement, 2002; 219041; 18 videocassettes (Box 20, Reel Project 68)
    Barcode: 31142042272933
  - 171st NYU Commencement, 2003; 219040; 12 videocassettes (Box 21, Reel Project 76)
  - 171st NYU Commencement, 2003; 243454; 3 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 71, Reel Project 76)
  - 171st NYU Commencement Master, 2003; 219039; 8 videocassettes (Box 22, Reel Project 76)
    Barcode: 31142042272958
  - 172nd NYU Commencement Master, 2004; 219038; 7 videocassettes (Box 23, Reel Project 78)
  - Gallatin Graduation 2004, 10 May 2004; 240602; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 71)
  - College of Arts & Sciences (CAS) Commencement Master, May 11, 2004; 219036; 3 videocassettes (Box 23, Reel Project 80)
  - 172nd NYU Commencement Master, 2004; 219035; 17 videocassettes (Box 24, Reel Project 78)
    Barcode: 31142042272974
  - 173rd NYU Commencement Master, 2005; 219034; 16 videocassettes (Box 25, Reel Project 81)
    Barcode: 31142042272982
  - 173rd NYU Commencement Master, 2005; 219033; 6 videocassettes (Box 26, Reel Project 81)
    Barcode: 31142042272990
  - NYU College of Arts and Science Bacculaureatre, 5 Dec 2005; 241137; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - CAS Baccalaureate Ceremony, 4 Dec 2006; 241138; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - 2006 Steinhardt Commencement Master, 22 Jun 2006; 239060; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 70)
  - Commencement Videotapes 2006, 219032; 22 videocassettes (Box 38)
  - Commencement Videotapes 2007, 219031; 14 videocassettes (Box 39)